An Icon Reborn.
Knight Rider is a science fiction, tv movie film directed by Steve Shill.
When a group of ruthless mercenaries kill a reclusive scientist, his creation, a new model of artificially
intelligent supercar, escapes to find his daughter and recruit a ex-soldier to thwart them.
Pilot for the reboot of the television series Knight Rider.
Mike Traceur, played by Justin Bruening.
Sarah Graiman, played by Deanna Russo.
Carrie Rivai, played by Sydney Tamiia Poitier.
Charles Graiman, played by Bruce Davison.
Welther, played by Greg Ellis.
Sheriff Ramsey, played by Chris Mulkey.
Knight Rider is a 2008 American made-for-television action film, which was created to serve as a backdoor pilot
for the new Knight Rider television series, a sequel to the 1982–1986 series of the same name.
This film makes no references to either the Knight Rider 2000 film or the
Team Knight Rider television series, instead as a reboot.
The film explores themes of artificial intelligence (a.i.),
conspiracy, reboot, gadget car, conspirators.
The tone is thought_provoking.